Craig McCorrisken Paisley, Renfrewshire 07745 794920

craigmccorrisken@gmail.com

Personal Profile

I am a 23-year-old, recent graduate, with a first-class honours degree in Computer Games Technology looking for a junior position in the gaming industry. For my dissertation, I developed a working 3D collision detection system using my version of the GJK algorithm, written in C++. This helped me develop my knowledge of C++, Visual Studio, Microsoft Word and source control.

I balanced my time at the university with a career as a Bar Supervisor where I learned to perform efficiently under pressure and work to a strict schedule all while managing and supporting the team I led.

Key Skills

- C++ Educated
- Experience Using C# and Java
- Experience working with IDE's: Mainly Visual Studio (also NetBeans & WebStorm)
- Experience Using source control (GitHub: Including Git GUI and Git Bash)

Employment History

Revolution Bar Group: Bar Supervisor

July 2018 - Current

Responsibilities: Team leading, time management, conflict resolution, critical thinking, effective communication between all levels of staff.

Pendulum Bar and Grill: Waiter

July 2017 – July 2018

Responsibilities: Customer satisfaction, restaurant cleanliness, working to a tight schedule

Glynhill Hotel and Leisure club: Bartender

November 2015 – July 2017

Responsibilities: Working as an Individual, opening and closing the bar, cash handling, customer safety, bar security, effective working in a fast-paced environment, day-to-day events.

Bean Grinder Café: Barista June 2015 – November 2015

Responsibilities: Food preparation, coffee making, closing standards, overall cleanliness.

Education

Further Education:

University of the West of Scotland (2017 - 2020)

Computer Game Technology - First-Class Honours

West College Scotland (2016 - 2017)

HND Games Development - A

West College Scotland (2015 - 2016)

HNC Games Development – A

High School Education:

- Higher Music A
- Higher Biology C
- Higher Mathematics C
- Higher English D

Extra Qualifications:

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

Hobbies & Interests

I currently spend my free time learning to use Unity and attempting to expand my knowledge of programming and the games industry.

Other hobbies include playing football, reading comics, practicing photography and playing guitar.

References

Marco Gilardi

Job Title: Lecturer at The University of the West of Scotland (Paisley)

Contact: Marco.Gilardi@uws.ac.uk

James Moore

Job Title: Senior Software Engineer at Veracity UK LTD

Contact: On request